http://www.outboardsales.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Contact Us
My Account
Welcome to OnlineOutboards.com!
Login
Create Account
0
Shopping Cart
Your cart is currently empty.
Extended Protection
Free Shipping (see details)
Monthly Payments
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Cumberland Watersports and www.OnlineOutboards.com respect the privacy of every individual who visits our website, responds to our advertisements or sends us e-mail communications. This Privacy Statement outlines the information we will collect and how we will use that information. We do not collect any personal information about you (such as your name, address, telephone number, or email address) unless you provide it to us voluntarily. Cumberland Watersports and www.OnlineOutboards.com will never sell or distribute your personal information to any third party except when necessary to complete the processing of your order (shipping carrier, warranty registration, etc…). We receive and store information you provide through our website or give us in any other way and you can choose not to provide certain information, however you may limit your ability to take advantage of many features offered through this website.
Security
Our secure online ordering form utilizes a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol to provide "secure sessions" for our users. Through the "secure session," information that you input into a www.OnlineOutboards.com secure order form will be sent and will arrive privately and unaltered. This security prohibits other companies and web users from being able to access your information. We value your privacy and strive to make this site as secure as possible for all of our customers. If you do not wish to use our secure online ordering form you can always complete your order by phone.
Quick Links
Cart
Search
My Account
About Us
Contact Us
Support & Help
Products FAQ
Sign up for our newsletter and be the first to know about coupons and special promotions.
© 2020 OnlineOutboards.com
